A Guide to the Peggy Sanford Carlin Papers, 1949-1966
Carlin (Peggy Sanford) Papers
1949-1966
Carlin, Peggy Sanford
2002-235
1 ft., 3 in.
Dolph Briscoe Center for American History, The University of Texas at Austin
Radio scripts written and broadcast in German to Austria by Peggy Sanford for Voice of America focusing on American customs, life, and culture between 1949 and 1966.
Scope and Contents
Radio scripts written and broadcast in German to Austria by Peggy Sanford for Voice of America focusing on American customs, life, and culture between 1949 and 1966. Programs include "Peggy Sanford Plaudert" ("Peggy Sandford Chats"), "Looking Across the Ocean," "Schauplatz Amerika," "Klatsch und Tratsch aus Amerika," movie columns and women's features.
Access Restrictions
Unrestricted access.
Index Terms
Subjects
Carlin, Peggy Sanford; Voice of America (organization); Radio broadcasting; Radio journalism; Women in radio broadcasting
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Voice of America scripts for the Austrian Unit by Peggy Sanford:
  - "Looking Across the Ocean,", August 1949 (Box 2J20)
  - "Peggy Sanford Plaudert" ("Peggy Sanford Chats"): (Box 2J20)
    - October 8, 1949-September 30, 1951 (Box 2J20)
    - October 5, 1951-September 24, 1953 (Box 2J21)
    - November 15, 1953-September 25, 1955 (Box 2J22)
    - Notes, undated (Box 2J22)
  - "Schauplatz Amerika," test scripts1965 (Box 2J22)
  - Movie columns by Peggy Sanford, 1957-1958 (Box 2J22)
  - Women's features by Peggy Sanford, 1960-1966 (Box 2J22)
  - "Klatsch und Tratsch aus Amerika,"undated (Box 2J22)